What you see is only half the story
Invisible Sister is a fantasy, adventure, comedy film directed by Paul Hoen.
Teenager Cleo's school science project goes quite awry, causing
her popular older sister Molly to go invisible.
Cleo, played by Rowan Blanchard.
Molly, played by Paris Berelc.
George, played by Karan Brar.
Nikki, played by Rachel Crow.
Molly's Best Friend, played by Ashton Smiley.
Molly's Friend, played by Devin Posey.
Invisible Sister is a 2015 American science fiction comedy film released as a Disney Channel
Original Movie and based on the book My Invisible Sister by Beatrice Colin and Sara Pinto.
The film is directed by Paul Hoen, and stars Rowan Blanchard and Paris Berelc.
It focuses on a student who turns her older sister
invisible due to a failed science project.
It premiered on October 9, 2015, and was viewed by 4.03 million people.
The tone is lighthearted.